<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
 <title>devo.ps</title>
 <link href='http://devo.ps//atom.xml' rel='self'/>
 <link href='http://devo.ps/'/>
 <updated>2014-09-25T03:33:21.098Z</updated>
 <id>http://devo.ps/</id>
 <author>
   <name>devo.ps</name>
   <email>info@devo.ps</email>
 </author>
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>Deploy Your Meteor Apps on Digital Ocean in 5 Minutes</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/deploy-your-meteor-apps-on-digital-ocean-in-5-minutes'/>
     <updated>2014-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/deploy-your-meteor-apps-on-digital-ocean-in-5-minutes</id>
     <content type='html'><p>Some of my colleagues and friends have been playing with Meteor for a few of their projects: so far they seem to love it, but when it came to hosting their app they didn&#39;t have a straight answer. They gave a quick try at the default Meteor hosting, Modulus.io and Heroku. But being the server nerd I am (and being massively in love with Digital Ocean), I thought I&#39;d look into how to self host Metero apps.</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>Releasing devo.ps 0.8.0</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0-8-0'/>
     <updated>2014-09-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0-8-0</id>
     <content type='html'><p>Today some exciting features with the release of <a href="http://devo.ps">devo.ps</a> 0.8.0. </p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>Releasing devo.ps 0.7.0</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0-7-0'/>
     <updated>2014-09-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0-7-0</id>
     <content type='html'><p>Another week, another release. We&#39;ve pushed devo.ps 0.7.0 out. A few things we fixed and added:</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>WTF Is DevOps?</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/wtf-is-devops'/>
     <updated>2014-09-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/wtf-is-devops</id>
     <content type='html'><p>I recently stumbled on an article by Jeff Knupp in my (ever growing) list of &quot;to read later&quot; bookmarks: <a href="http://jeffknupp.com/blog/2014/04/15/how-devops-is-killing-the-developer/">How &#39;DevOps&#39; is Killing the Developer</a>. In a nutshell, he makes the point that the DevOps movement, and its reliance on cross-functional profiles (aka &quot;full stack&quot; engineers) is fair in a startup environment where resource attrition favors Jack-of-all-trades, but is a poor strategy for larger and more resourceful established businesses. I think it misses the point entirely. More importantly, it goes along the lines of a lot of criticism and misunderstanding many other voiced with regards to DevOps.</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>Releasing devo.ps 0.6.0</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0-6-0'/>
     <updated>2014-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0-6-0</id>
     <content type='html'><p>We just pushed another devo.ps release (0.6.0). We are nearing a stable build and will most likely spend the next week adding more trigger for events (cron, GitHub events, devo.ps events...) and add more technologies. We have a few large updates to the documentation that should go live by next Wedneday as well.</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>Metalsmith On GitHub pages</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/metalsmith-on-github-pages'/>
     <updated>2014-09-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/metalsmith-on-github-pages</id>
     <content type='html'><p>We love GitHub pages and use it more than we probably should: our <a href="http://devo.ps">main website (devo.ps)</a> and <a href="http://docs.devo.ps">documentation</a> are actually GitHub pages. We use <a href="https://swiftype.com/">SwiftType</a> to provide search on the documentation, but otherwise these are pretty regular static websites. However, we don&#39;t use Jekyll; our team is more at ease with nNde.js than Ruby, which is why we usually prefer it <a href="http://www.metalsmith.io/">Metalsmith</a>. And since we&#39;re pretty lazy, we automate building and pushing to the <code>gh-pages</code> using <a href="http://devo.ps">devo.ps</a> (of course). Here&#39;s what it looks like.</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>Basic Setup For A New Linux Server</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/basic-setup-for-a-new-linux-server'/>
     <updated>2014-09-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/basic-setup-for-a-new-linux-server</id>
     <content type='html'><p>You just provisioned a new machine on AWS or Digital Ocean. It almost has that new car smell: great. Now what? You want to go from a vanilla install to a box that you&#39;ll be able to easily manage and has the <a href="http://devo.ps/blog/troubleshooting-5minutes-on-a-yet-unknown-box/">basic tools for troubleshootint it</a>. Let me share a few of the best practices we stick to when creating servers with <a href="http://devo.ps">devo.ps</a>. You should <a href="https://app.devo.ps">sign up for a free account</a> by the way: you&#39;ll get all of what I&#39;m about to list set up on your own Rackspace, Digital Ocean, Linode or AWS servers in a few minutes.</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>Dealing With Servers Still Sucks</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/dealing-with-servers-still-suck'/>
     <updated>2014-09-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/dealing-with-servers-still-suck</id>
     <content type='html'><p>The idea of dealing with servers is almost invariably cringe-inducing for developers. Sure, I know a few folks (me and my colleagues at <a href="http://devo.ps">devo.ps</a> included) who actually get a kick out of it. But by and large, setting up infrastructure isn&#39;t the developer&#39;s favorite. There&#39;s definitely been a lot of awesome innovation in the past few years that made the whole thing manageable, especially with services like Heroku or TravisCI. But they are no silver bullets. At the end of the day, the whole experience sucks less, but it isn&#39;t near being enjoyable.</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>One-Click Deploy Of Your Infrastructure</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/one-click-deploy-of-your-infrastructure'/>
     <updated>2014-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/one-click-deploy-of-your-infrastructure</id>
     <content type='html'><p>We just released <a href="http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0.5.0/">devo.ps 0.5.0</a> and are pretty excited about one feature in particular.</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
   <entry>
     <title>Releasing devo.ps 0.5.0</title>
     <link href='http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0.5.0'/>
     <updated>2014-09-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
     <id>http://devo.ps/blog/releasing-devops-0.5.0</id>
     <content type='html'><p>We just released a new version of devo.ps (0.5.0). We are very excited to start rolling out the <strong><a href="devo.ps/blog/one-click-deploy-of-your-infrastructure/">devo.ps button</a></strong> which allows our users to deploy entire infrastructures without leaving the browser with little or no configuration. more on this soon.</p></content>
   </entry>
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
</feed>